ADAPTED FROM DEMON KING
OF JINJIANG LITERATURE CITY
ORIGINAL WORK BY JIULU FEIXIANG
Orchid.
My lord!
Didn't you drink Fairy Orchid's
Dream of Nine Serenities?
Why are you still in pain?
Since we are to be husband and wife,
we must stay together
until death do us part
for better or for worse.
Even though
I cannot bear this trial for her,
how can I let her suffer alone?
My lord.
My lord!
Where is she?
Where is the Fairy Tribe woman?
Come out!
Come out now!
Let her out!
Lord Xunfeng,
unless the tortured person
voluntarily gives up,
the punishment cannot be stopped.
Give up!
You can't hold on anymore.
Come out now!
Answer me!
She doesn't have the strength to speak.
Open the sarcophagus now!
Fairy Orchid.
I'll count to ten.
If you aren't giving up,
knock twice on the sarcophagus.
One.
Two.
- It's so pretty.
- It's so beautiful.
What are you doing?
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Look, it's Cloud-Whale.
My lord.
Get up.
The three-day sentence is up.
Open the sarcophagus.
- Greetings, Moon Queen.
My lord, as Shuiyuntian's God of War,
the immortal criminal, Changheng,
has disregarded his duties,
violated heavenly laws,
broken marriage engagement,
and communicated with a spy
yet refuses to admit his guilt.
The law will not tolerate this.
He should be immediately sent
to Immortal Slaying Pavilion
for execution.
Wait.
After all, Changheng is the son
of our father, Lord Dong.
Before execution,
all must be accounted for.
From this moment on,
Changheng is stripped of his immortal rank
and deposed.
You are no longer
the son of our father, Lord Dong.
You will have no clan, no surname,
and will not be worshipped after death
or included in the Heavenly Tablet.
Your name will be removed forever
from the genealogy
of Shuiyuntian's immortals,
just like your deserter mother.
All fault lies with me!
Lord Changheng is innocent.
Danyin, step down!
Orchid is the Goddess of Xishan
who has been missing for 30,000 years.
The Xilan Holy Seal.
It purifies evil qi.
She is indeed the goddess.
In order to save Orchid,
Lord Changheng
repeatedly visited the Cangyan Sea.
It was not in defiance of the rules
or for a love affair.
It was because of the destined marriage.
I knew long ago
that Orchid is the Goddess of Xishan.
I once saw
the scenes of two weddings
between Lord Changheng and Orchid
in the Tianji Mirror at Arbiter Hall.
One was the tribulation
in the Mortal World.
The other was when Lord Changheng
and the Goddess of Xishan
were surrounded and blessed
by all from the Fairy Realm
at their wedding by the Oblivion River.
The Tianji Mirror reveals the future.
It never makes a mistake.
Orchid is the Goddess of Xishan.
Why did you wait until now to reveal this?
I am
in love with Lord Changheng.
I didn't want him to find the goddess
and fulfill the engagement.
So I kept this a secret.
I was selfish.
I disregarded the big picture.
I chased after my selfish desires,
which led to a big mistake.
Please, my lord.
Spare Lord Changheng.
The one to go to Immortal Slaying Pavilion
should be me.
Danyin, get up.
Lord Changheng.
I'm sorry.
You did nothing wrong.
What Changheng said is correct.
Fairy Danyin has found the goddess.
She has made up for her mistake.
The Goddess of Xishan has been
defending the three realms for generations
against the Evil God Taisui.
Changheng risked his life many times
to save the goddess.
It was a righteous act.
Heavenly law and fate
are indeed unfathomable.
Changheng is not guilty.
He should return
to his position as God of War.
Lord Changheng,
welcome back
to the position of God of War.
My lord,
this is the confession
written by imprisoned criminal Ronghao.
According to Ronghao,
the Moon Tribe has rampantly
invaded our borders
and slaughtered
3,000 of our heavenly soldiers.
If this is not avenged,
how can the soldiers' souls rest in peace?
Please send troops to the Cangyan Sea
to avenge our tribesmen.
- Avenge our tribesmen!
Ronghao.
Why did you lie?
You're here.
Why did you blame the Moon Tribe
for the 3,000 soldiers' deaths
and start a war?
There is only plain tea in the prison.
Do you want to drink with me?
Answer me!
You already know the answer.
Why do you need to ask me?
Does it really matter to your brother
why 3,000 heavenly soldiers
were slaughtered?
I merely offered him
a reason that he wanted.
It wouldn't do him any good
to execute a lay immortal like me.
However,
if it were Dongfang Qingcang
who killed 3,000 heavenly soldiers,
he could unite Shuiyuntian
under this excuse to dispatch troops.
Your brother can then send troops
to the Cangyan Sea
and raze it to the ground.
I won't let him get his way.
The Moon Tribe has suffered
from years of civil war.
Their army is weak.
But Dongfang Qingcang is very powerful.
He can manipulate Hellfire.
His power alone
can defeat an army of 10,000.
So if you,
the God of War, don't join the war,
your brother
absolutely will not act rashly.
Isn't that so?
What's your point?
Dongfang Qingcang
can no longer command Hellfire.
What?
That day at the Oblivion River,
he was only momentarily injured.
How can he be unable to command Hellfire?
So whether you want to or not,
this war
will happen.
And you
will definitely join in.
And you're destined to fight.
Because we are both the same.
I have no choice.
In the end, you have no choice either.
You have no choice?
You chose to conspire with my brother
to incite chaos
and instigate the biggest war
in the three realms in millennia!
Ronghao.
If you still think of me as a friend,
tell me what you are hiding.
Is everything you've done
truly just to resurrect
the former God of War?
Smart people never get good endings.
Changheng,
I can lie to the whole world.
But I will never lie to you.
It might be good for you
not to know the reason.
- Jieli.
- I have things to do.
Why do you keep following me?
Then why do you keep avoiding me?
I'm not.
Yes, you are.
Lately, whenever I find you,
you're either busy or going to bed.
We don't talk for long when we meet.
I feel that we're growing apart.
I really do have something to do.
I have to look
at wedding dress materials for Orchid.
- I can't be late.
- Hold on.
Jieli.
I have to tell you
something very important.
What is this?
This is the key to my cellar.
All my savings over the years
are in there.
And my future salary too.
It's all yours.
What's wrong with you?
Take it back.
Hear me out.
I know
I have very little money.
It might not be to your liking.
But today, I want you to understand
that I want to give you everything I have.
I want to give you
all the good things in this world.
Because I want
to marry you, Jieli.
Don't feel awkward.
I know I may not reach your standards.
But after telling you
everything I want to say,
I feel much better.
Your meager salary
isn't even enough to buy a nice house.
That's true.
But my lord has said it.
He's going to increase my salary.
On your salary,
you'll never be able
to afford a bride-dowry.
How can you marry me?
You're right.
So
after we get married,
I'll run a business.
You'll be in charge of inventory,
running errands, helping out,
and soliciting business.
And I won't give you a cut anymore.
All profits will go to me.
Stupid Black Dragon, do you hear me?
"After we get married?"
Jieli.
Do you agree to marry me?
What else could I mean?
- Be gentler.
- This is great!
- You've agreed to marry me!
- Put me down, Stupid Black Dragon!
I'm getting dizzy!
The big war is coming.
You've been preparing all night.
You must be exhausted.
It's you.
You once promised
to repay my lord for saving your family.
Now that my lord is in trouble,
it's time for you to fulfill your promise.
I did make a promise.
But it was made
to the lay immortal Ronghao,
not the Lord of Haishi.
Not only do I refuse to help the evildoer,
but I shall also capture you,
a remnant of the evil of Haishi.
I had destroyed that with my own hands.
How did it end up in your hands?
Could it be…
Neither the Fairy Tribe nor the Moon Tribe
will tolerate them.
Our only option now
is to make one fully a fairy
and assimilate the other
into the Moon Tribe.
Ever since that night,
I've been searching for Xingluo.
But I never heard back from her.
It was you people.
It was you people who hid Xingluo
and my other daughter.
Your wife was weakened from childbirth.
She died as she was fleeing.
It was my lord
who took the child away and raised her.
Now that you have
the whereabouts of your daughter,
you should be happy.
You…
You've lied to me for so many years.
What does he want me to do?
This task should not be difficult for you.
Get my lord out of Karma Jail.
- Greetings, Moon Queen.
Get up first.
Shangque.
Greetings, Moon Queen.
Shangque, why are you doing this too?
Get up.
Shangque, get up now.
Do you hear me?
Get up.
Yes, Moon Queen.
And them too.
You may all go.
Fairy Orchid.
Have you seen Jieli?
She just went out.
All right.
Then get some rest, Fairy Orchid.
Hold on.
Do you have the feeling
that Jieli has been acting strange lately?
Now that you mention it,
I think…
She treated me to sugar cakes yesterday
and paid for it.
There's more.
On the Mountain and Moon Festival,
she gave me
50% of the spirit stones she earned.
So it wasn't my imagination.
Look.
This is the dowry she gifted me.
For nothing. Free.
And she said
that I'm free of all my previous debts.
That's so nice of her.
Fairy Orchid,
do you know what the strangest thing is?
It is
that I asked her to marry me
and she said yes.
But she didn't ask for a bride-dowry.
- Really?
- Yes.
Shangque, do you think Jieli is possessed?
Possessed?
No evil thing dares
to cause trouble
with my lord here in Silent Moon Palace.
You're right.
I get it.
Jieli grew up alone
and had to work hard to survive in Haishi.
She had no one to turn to.
She has suffered so much.
Only a lot of money
can bring her a sense of security.
So in the past,
she had to fuss over every bit of money.
But things are different now.
She has someone she loves
and a good friend like me.
From now on,
Silent Moon Palace will be her home.
Now that her situation is different,
her frame of mind is different.
Naturally, she will change.
Then…
I must treat her better than ever.
Of course.
If you dare to treat Jieli badly,
I'll be the first to hunt you down.
I won't.
Look at the hairpin that Jieli gave me.
Isn't it beautiful?
It is.
Lord Xunfeng.
How are you?
How dare you come here?
Don't you want to know
why the Moon Supreme's Hellfire
still hasn't recovered?
Fairy Orchid,
my lord invites you to a banquet.
It is almost time.
- Greetings, my lord.
Orchid.
My husband, there you are.
What's the matter with you?
My dear.
You have kept me waiting.
You are not Orchid.
Who are you?
Moon Supreme,
I have an important matter to report.
Lord Xunfeng,
my lord doesn't want to see you.
Greetings, my lord.
Greetings, Moon Queen.
Why?
Why are you always interrupting us?
My lord.
How did this happen?
The Bone Orchid was made
from my heart's blood.
If she is not deeply in love with me,
the Bone Orchid is just
an ordinary protective artifact.
However,
if she is devoted to me,
the Bone Orchid
will not be able to be taken off.
Taking it by force
would cause her mortal harm.
So she is already deeply in love with you.
Lady Chidi's spirit still exists
and is in the Bone Orchid?
Moon Supreme,
we could bring back the 100,000 soldiers
in the Xuanxu Realm.
But why haven't you
taken off the Bone Orchid?
Do you think I don't want to?
The fragmented spirit of Lady Chidi
is using the Bone Orchid
to feed on her spiritual power.
If I don't take it off,
in less than ten days,
when Lady Chidi's spirit is restored,
she will die of exhaustion.
Does this mean
that Moon Queen won't live long?
If her life is not preserved,
then my lord's life will also…
Moon Supreme,
I have a solution.
We've found
the last fragment of the Chengying Sword.
The Chengying Sword has been recast.
How can it be?
The Moon Queen loves you deeply.
She would kill herself
with the Chengying Sword
to save your life.
Give me the Chengying Sword.
Do you want to destroy it?
Hand it over.
I cannot do it.
You are the Moon Tribe's last hope.
Your life must not be compromised.
Hand it over!
Moon Supreme!
Only by obtaining Lady Chidi's spirit
can we save
the 100,000 soldiers in Xuanxu Realm.
We've already failed once.
We can't fail a second time!
Today, a spy reported
that Shuiyuntian
has already raised their troops
and is ready to start a full-scale war.
If the 100,000 soldiers can't return,
the Moon Tribe will face annihilation,
Moon Supreme!
If I could protect you by dying,
I would not hesitate to do so.
After Moon Queen joins our tribe,
she should have
a greater sense of self-sacrifice!
That's what I call a worthy death!
Shut up!
I will never sacrifice her!
I will think of another way.
No wonder.
No wonder Father was resolved to die
to rid you of emotions!
Watch your words, Lord Xunfeng.
If I had known this would happen,
I would have died by your Hellfire Sword
rather than see you
become a good-for-nothing
who has the wrong priorities!
Lord Xunfeng!
Dongfang Qingcang.
Take your time
thinking about your strategy here.
I will leave.
I almost forgot.
I've already found out
that you cultivated Hellfire
by ridding yourself of emotions.
Now that you're engrossed in love
and your emotions returned,
the Hellfire has naturally disappeared.
As you are now,
you're no longer
the supreme one admired and worshipped
by all in the three realms.
My lord.
Lord Xunfeng was just being impulsive.
He only said that about the Hellfire
in the heat of the moment.
I had already guessed it.
I just didn't want to face it.
I dare not imagine
how I can protect
the people of the Cangyan Sea or her
without Hellfire.
Stupid Black Dragon.
Why isn't he here yet?
He's so slow.
Greetings, Pavilion Master.
Where is the goddess?
What you don't know is that
Qingcang has recently assigned more guards
to protect Orchid.
I'm afraid that acting rashly
would expose me
and spoil my lord's plan.
That's enough.
You've repeatedly come up with excuses.
You must've forgotten the effects
of the Heart-Eroding Pill's poison.
Pavilion Master, please spare my life.
If you bring the goddess out,
I'll completely cure you of the poison.
You would rather die?
You two sure are close.
But I am curious.
If you had to choose one person,
would you choose your friend
or your man?
What did you do to Shangque?
Where is he?
He was just poisoned
by my Butterfly-Scale Poison.
Jieli.
Why are you here?
I'll give you three days' worth
of the Heart-Eroding Pill's antidote.
After three days,
if you haven't brought the goddess out,
you and your man
will succumb to the poison together.
Moreover,
he will die more painfully than you.
Jieli.
Where have you been?
What took you so long?
I'm sorry.
It wasn't on purpose.
I just--
Why did you pull on my collar?
A mole on the shoulder
means poverty for life.
I was checking your luck with wealth.
That's nonsense.
What's wrong with you?
Why are your eyes red?
It's all because of you.
You took so long to get here.
Sand got into my eyes.
I'm sorry.
On the way here,
I saw a crispy candy shop.
I wanted to buy some for you.
But the candy wasn't ready yet.
So I waited there for a while.
Let me tell you.
This candy must be eaten while it's hot.
Why is it all crushed to pieces?
It's fine.
It still tastes the same.
It's still sweet.
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
I just feel that
although I held it carefully in my arms
and protected it,
it was still crushed.
It doesn't seem like a good sign.
You said I was talking nonsense,
but you're the one
with a wild imagination.
Maybe my imagination is running wild.
But I really hope
that my lord, Fairy Orchid,
you, and I
can all be well
and have everything go smoothly.
What's wrong with Orchid?
Nothing.
Stupid Black Dragon,
you don't know how to lie.
You've been preoccupied
for the past few days.
You even feared a bad sign.
I want to hear the truth.
Jieli, I really can't tell you.
Don't ask.
After you agreed to marry me,
I was so happy that I couldn't sleep.
But lately, I don't know what it is.
I keep feeling a tightness in my chest.
Maybe this all feels too blissful.
It doesn't seem real.
What are you talking about?
Stupid Black Dragon,
are you having regrets?
Do you think I'm a miser or a spendthrift?
How can that be?
Maybe it's the unstable situation lately.
War could start at any moment.
I fear that if I don't make it back,
I won't be able to protect you.
Take it back!
What are you talking about?
Stupid Black Dragon,
I'm telling you.
You must live peacefully to old age.
Nothing can happen to you.
Do you hear me?
Promise me.
I'll keep you safe.
For the past 30,000 years,
the Moon Tribe has been disunited
and leaderless.
That is why Shuiyuntian was able
to seize our territories.
Now that my lord has returned,
the Moon Tribe is once again united
and of one mind.
This is the time
for us to take revenge
and crush the Fairy Realm!
- Take revenge!
- Crush the Fairy Realm!
But the previous plan
to free the 100,000 soldiers
has failed.
Now we face
an army of 200,000 menacing fairies.
We are outnumbered.
I'm afraid our outlook is bleak.
In my opinion,
we should give up Silver Lake
and retreat to Ninth You.
What do you think, Moon Supreme?
Lord Xunfeng, what are you talking about?
Do you want to cede more land?
In the past 30,000 years,
haven't we lost enough territory?
The lord has returned now.
Although we don't have enough troops,
each of our warriors is brave enough
to be worth ten.
Besides,
we still have the lord.
That's right.
The lord's Hellfire
can take out an army of 10,000 on its own.
We might not lose this battle!
But what if we lose?
The people of the Moon Tribe
are not cowards!
If we lose,
we will willingly follow the lord
and die on the battlefield!
- Kill the enemy!
- Wipe out our shame!